{
    "subject": "Louise_Mountbatten",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gustaf_VI_Adolf_of_Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Louise Mountbatten is married to Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9438338875770569,
            "question": "Who is Louise Mountbatten married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9386799335479736,
            "question": "Who was Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9094701409339905,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Louise Mountbatten and Gustaf VI Adolf?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950359225273132,
            "question": "Was Louise Mountbatten Swedish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8810550570487976,
            "question": "To whom was Louise Mountbatten wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8277966380119324,
            "question": "What is the name of Louise Mountbatten's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.803072988986969,
            "question": "Who was Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5125062465667725,
            "question": "Is Louise Mountbatten connected to royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4949931800365448,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Louise Mountbatten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47845134139060974,
            "question": "What country was Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden the ruler of?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louise Mountbatten is married to Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden.",
            "html": "yago_25465_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Louise Mountbatten?",
            "html": "yago_25465_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Louise Mountbatten connected to royalty?",
            "html": "yago_25465_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden?",
            "html": "yago_25465_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25465_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents mention that Lady Louise Mountbatten was engaged to Crown Prince Gustaf Adolf of Sweden (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25465/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt).\n* They also state that Crown Prince Gustaf Adolf of Sweden married Lady Louise Mountbatten in 1923 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25465/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25465/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt).\n* Additionally, the documents mention that Louise Mountbatten was Queen of Sweden from 1950 until her death in 1965 as the wife of King Gustaf VI Adolf (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25465/re-ranker-msmarco/59.txt).\n\nAll these pieces of information collectively support the triple \"Louise Mountbatten is married to Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe the marriage between Louise Mountbatten and Crown Prince Gustaf Adolf of Sweden, not King Gustaf VI Adolf. While it's noted that Gustaf Adolf became King after his father Gustaf V, the specific mention in the provided context does not support the statement that Louise Mountbatten was married to Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Louise Mountbatten married Crown Prince Gustaf Adolf of Sweden, who later became King Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden upon Louise\u2019s accession to the throne. They were not married to each other as stated in the incorrect fact.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}